Henry Allen Moe Papers 1920-1975 Mss.B.M722
American Philosophical Society
- Henry Allen Moe Papers, 1920-1975; 120 lin. feet (Box 1-344)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MOMA)
    - Meeting, November 13, 1974
    - Meeting: committee on the Museum collections
    - Membership report
    - Minutes
    - Minutes. Annual meeting of corporation
    - Minutes. Board of trustees
    - Minutes. Corporation
    - Minutes. Executive and coordination committees and Board of Trustees
    - Minutes. Exhibition committee and Board of Trustees
    - Minutes. Finance committee
    - Minutes. International Council
    - Minutes. Meetings of coordination committee
    - Minutes. Photography committee
    - Minutes. Proposed budget
    - Minutes. Reports
    - Minutes. Special corporation meeting and Board of Trustees
    - Minutes. of spring meeting
    - Minutes. Staff
    - National circulating exhibitions
    - Operating budget; acquisitions list
    - Personnel policy and procedure
    - Photography
    - Photography Memorandum
    - Policy report
    - Press releases
    - Proposal for an art lending library
    - Proposed budget
    - Publications activities
    - Report, Circulating exhibitions
    - Report on international activities
    - Report on policy
    - Report to ad hoc committee
    - Report to the Ford Foundation
    - Reports
    - Resumes
    - Rubenstein, Sarah
    - Salary program
    - Staff information
    - Staff compensation
    - Staff salaries
    - Staff organization
    - Thirtieth anniversary drive
    - Trustee committees
  - Music matters
  - Musser, John M
  - Myers
  - Myers, George S
  - Myers, Lucy A
  - Myers, O Jay
  - Myers, Otto J
  - Myers, W I
  - N, H
  - Nadelman, Elie
  - Nagel, Charles
  - Nahm, Milton C
  - Naisner, E W
  - Nakian, Reuben
  - Nambiar, O K
  - Nanney, David Young
  - Naramore, Elaine
  - Narancio, Martin Miqueo
  - Naromi Land Trust
  - Nason, John W
  - Nassau County Historical Museum
  - Nater, Jean M
  - Nater, Timothy
  - Natestad, Harold D
  - Nathan, Hans
  - Nathan Trunk Company
  - National Academy of Sciences
  - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council
  - National Art Workers Community
  - National Audubon Society
  - National center for information on careers in education
  - National City Bank
  - National Committee for a Free Europe
  - National Council on the Arts
  - National Council on Community Foundations
  - National Council on the Humanities
    - Meetings
    - Minutes
    - Moe, Henry Allen
    - Reports
  - National Cyclopedia of American Biography
  - National Education Association
  - National Endowment for the Arts
  - National Endowment for the Humanities
    - American Issues Forum
    - Application review panels
    - Applications
    - Appropriations
    - Committee on planning
    - Communications panel
    - Congress
    - Continuation of Museum Intern program
    - Continuation of regional experiments program.
    - Control sheets
    - Council
    - Division of education
    - Education program
    - Explanation to president
    - Fellowships and stipends
    - Fellowships recommended
    - Funding (grants)
    - Funds
    - Guidelines for evaluating applications
    - House appropriations committee
    - Keeney, Barnaby C
    - Meeting
    - Mexican Americans
    - Minutes
    - Miscellany
    - Moe, Henry Allen
    - Perkins, Kathleen T
    - Program information
    - Proposal from university presses
    - Release
    - Research and publication
    - Ripley, S Dillon
    - Status of funds
    - Status report
    - Summary of recommendations
    - Teaching internship
    - University and community
  - National Foundation on the Arts and the Humanities
  - National Gallery of Art
  - National Gallery of Scotland
  - National Humanities Faculty
  - National Institute of Public Affairs
  - National Medal of Science
  - National Music League
  - National Repertory Theatre
    - Educational program
    - Educational report
  - National Research Center of the Arts
  - National Science Foundation
  - National Science Foundation Commission
  - National Society for Autistic Children, Inc.
  - National Surety Corporation
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation
  - National Urban Coalition
  - National Youth Science Center
  - Nature
  - Nature Conservatory of Connecticut
  - Navarra, Charles
  - Navy Department
  - Naylor, Henry
  - Neece, Harold V
  - Negbaur, H K
  - Nelbach, Philip E
  - Nelson, Mrs. Betty
  - Nelson, Charles A
  - Nelson, Mrs. Joyce
  - Nelson, Marcia
  - Nelson, Nil
  - Nelson, Robert E
  - Nelson, William
  - Nesser, Thomas
  - Netanyahu, B
  - Netzer, Royal F
  - Neurosciences Research Program
  - Neutra, Dion
  - Neutra, Richard J
  - Nevins, Allan
  - New York Board of Trade
  - New York Botanical Garden
  - New York Central Railroad
  - New York City Arts Festival
  - New York City Committee for Latin-American scholarships
  - New York City Cultural Council
  - New York Community Trust
  - New York Foundation for the Arts
  - New York Friends Group
  - New York Herald Tribune
  - New York Medical College
  - New York Public Library
  - New York School of Social Work
  - New York Shakespeare Festival
  - New York State American Revolution Bicentennial Commission
  - New York State Art Program
  - New York State Association of Museums
  - New York State Association of Museums Council
    - Salary survey
  - New York State Citizens Committee for the Public Schools
  - New York State College of Ceramics
  - New York State Commission on Cultural Resources
  - New York State Council on the Arts
    - Applications
    - Architectural,environmental arts
    - Artists
    - Dewey, Kenneth G
    - Directorship
    - Funding
    - Iroquois
    - Janus report
    - Larrabee, Eric
    - Minutes
    - Performing arts program
    - Program
    - Publicity release
    - Release
    - Report of enquiry into state aid to Museums
    - Report on the Bicentennial
    - Services and funding
    - Tarreytown
    - Wampum
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation
  - New York State Department of Social Welfare
  - New York State Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement
  - New York State Historical Association
    - AASLH Seminars
    - Acting director's report
    - Annual account
    - Annual meeting
    - Annual Yonkers convention
    - Budget
    - Cooperstown
    - Cooperstown. Financial statements
    - Cooperstown graduate program
    - Counter attack
    - Director's report
    - Farmers' Museum
    - Financial report
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt Museum
    - Grants
    - Headquarters House, Ticonderoga
    - Meeting of Board of Trustees
    - Special accounts
    - Ticonderoga
    - Welsh, Peter C
  - New York State Rehabilitation Hospital
  - New York Times
  - New York University
  - New Yorker cartoons
  - Newcomb, Rexford
  - Newhall, Beaumont
  - Newlin, A Chauncey
  - Newman, Fred O
  - Newton, Carl Eldridge
  - Newton, William Eldridge
  - Nicholas, J S
  - Nichols, J P
  - Nichols, Jeannette
  - Nichols, Roy Franklin
  - Nickerson, Ruth
  - Nickles, Roger
  - Nicol, H Gilbert
  - Nicolais, Mrs. Margaret
  - Nicolais, Michael
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold
  - Nielson, George E
  - Niemeyer, John H
  - Nieter, Royal
  - Niles, Emory H
  - Niles, Mrs. Katherine
  - Niles, Russell D
  - Nisbet, Ada
  - Nisbet, Robert
  - Nitze, William A
  - Nixon, Richard Milhouse
  - Noble, Edward John, Foundation
  - Noble, G Bernard
  - Noble, Joseph V
  - Noble, W H
  - Nock, Arthur D
  - Noguchi, Isamu
  - Nolla, José A B
  - Nolla, Mrs. Olga
  - Nolte, Richard H
  - Noonan, Julia A
  - Norberta, Sister Mary
  - Norman, Dorothy
  - Norrington
  - North, Helen
  - Northam, Alice
  - Northrop, F S C
  - Norton, Frances Alice
  - Norton, W. W., and Company
  - Norton, Mrs. William Warder
  - Norvelle, Lee
  - Norwood, Juanita
  - Notestein, Wallace
  - Nourse, Edwin G
  - Nourse, Joseph
  - Nourse, Margaret
  - Novak, Mary Ann
  - Noyes, Alexander Dana
  - Oakes, John B
  - Oakes, Whitney
  - Oakley, J M
  - Oaths
  - Ober, Harold
  - Oberbeck, S K
  - Oberlaender Trust
    - Applications
    - Minutes, 1931
    - with Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation
  - Oberlin College
  - O'Brien, Olive
  - O'Bryan, Deric
  - Obuchowski, Chester W
  - Ochoa, Severo
  - O'Connor, Parke
  - Odaniell, Robert
  - Odyssey Award
  - Oenslager, Donald
  - Office of Scientific Research and Development
    - Appointment of committee
    - Army
    - British and Russian
    - Bush report
    - Correspondence
    - Educational proposals
    - Educational pyramid
    - Frank, L K
    - General
    - Loan funds
    - Other committees
    - Palmer committee
    - Publicity
    - Scholarships
    - Science education
    - Selection procedure
    - Talent search
    - Wilson, E B
  - O'Flaherty, Hal
  - Ogg, Campbell
  - O'Gorman, Edmundo
  - O'Gorman, Ned
  - O'Hara, Bishop John
  - O'Kane, Walter C
  - O'Keefe, James
  - O'Keefe, John
  - O'Kelly, Bernard
  - Old Authors Farm, Ltd.
  - Oldberg, Eric
  - Oldenburg, Richard E
  - Olds, Irving S
  - Oler, Mrs. Clarke K
  - Olivar-Bertrand, R
  - Oliver, David B
  - Oliver, Eli
  - Oliver, James
  - Olsen, Lillian N
  - Olson, Clairebelle B
  - Olson, Emery
  - Open Channel
  - Opie, Peter
  - Oppenheimer, Jane
  - O'Quin, Miss
  - Ortiz, Fernando
  - Orton, Dwayne
  - Ortúzar, Ramón
  - Osborn, Gardner
  - Osborn, James E
  - Osborne, Mary Tom
  - Osgood, Mrs.
  - Osgood, Claude Jack
  - Osler, Chester
  - Oslo Sparebank
  - Osver, Arthur
  - Otesaga and Cooper Inn
  - Othman, Frederick C
  - Otsego County Area Occupational Center
  - Otto, Mrs. Celia Jackson
  - Outhwaite, Leonard
  - Outhwaite, Lucille and Leonard
  - Overbey, Erik Per
  - Overmyer, Calvin J
  - Owen, G E L
  - Owings, Nathaniel
  - Owsley, Frank Lawrence
  - Oxford University
    - Appeal
    - Law library
    - Meeting of July 1, 1970
    - Press
    - St. Catherine's College
  - Oxonian
  - Pabst Brewing Company
  - Pace, Charles Nelson
  - Pachas, E S
  - Paddock, Willard
  - Page, Arthur W
  - Page, Mrs. Malcolm
  - Painter, Ann
  - Painter, Sidney
  - Pais, Maria Luisa
  - Paisley Press
  - Pajaro, Eliseo
  - Palamountain, Mrs. Joseph C
  - Paley, William S
  - Palm, Erwin Walter
  - Palmer, A Kenny C
  - Palmer, Mrs. A Kenny C
  - Palmer, R R
  - Palmer, Walter W
  - Pan American World Airways
  - Pantaleo, Gito
  - Pantheon Books
  - Papers of John Marshall
  - Papers of Thomas Jefferson
  - Pappenheimer, A
  - Pargellis, Stanley
  - Paris, Dorothy
  - Parish, Ernest C
  - Park, Mrs. Edwin Avery
  - Parker, Dorothy
  - Parker, Robert C
  - Parkin Archives
  - Parkin, G Raleigh
  - Parkinson, Mrs. Eliza Bliss
  - Parkinson, John
  - Parkinson, T I
  - Parkinson, Thomas
  - Parran, Thomas
  - Parrish, Harcourt
  - Parrott, Rae Beth
  - Parry, C F
  - Parry, John
  - Parsons, Carl
  - Parsons, Mrs. Carle Tyler
  - Parsons, Geoffrey
  - Parsons, Geoffrey, Jr.
  - Parvin, W Rodman
  - Parvin, Mrs. W Rodman
  - Pascal, Ernest
  - Patino, Victor Manuel
  - Patman, Wright
  - Paton, John W
  - Patrick, James
  - Patrina, Carlotta
  - Pattee, James Joseph
  - Pattee, Richard
  - Patterson, Elmore C
  - Patterson, John O
  - Patterson, Robert Lee
  - Patterson, Robert Lee, Jr.
  - Patton, Mrs. George S, Jr.
  - Pattullo, N A
  - Paul, K G
  - Paul, Robert S
  - Pauling, Linus
  - Paulsen, T S
  - Payson, Charles Shipman
  - Paz, Alberto
  - Peacocke, A R
  - Pearce, Eleanor G
  - Peck, Taylor
  - Pekeris, C L
  - Pell, H G
  - Pell, John G G
  - Pellegrini, Antonio
  - Penfield, Wilder
  - Penikett, E J K
  - Peninsula Bank and Trust Company
  - Penn, Christopher
  - Penney, J C
  - Pennsylvania Railroad
  - Pennsylvania State University
  - Pepinsky, Ray
  - Performers' Committee for Twentieth-Century Music
  - Performing Arts Letters
  - Performing Arts Panel
  - Perkins, Fred B
  - Perkins, Kathleen
  - Perkins, Philip Laurence
  - Perrot, Paul N
  - Perry, Bernard B
  - Perry, Julia
  - Persha, Mrs. Mary M
  - Peterson
  - Peterson, M D
  - Peterson, Peter G
  - Petter, Mrs. Jay Harry
  - Pettingill, Mrs. W H
  - Pettis, Russell
  - Pettit, Frederick de Len
  - Peyre, Henri
  - Pfaffmann, Carl
  - Pfeiffer, John E
  - Pfeiffer, Matilde
  - Phi Beta Kappa
  - Philadelphia Museum College of Arts
  - Philippines
  - Philips, John B
  - Phillips, Donald R
  - Phillips, John Goldsmith
  - Phillips, Michael
  - Phillips, Mike
  - Phillips, Mrs. Rose
  - Philosopher in the Park
  - Phoenix Theatre
  - Piel, Gerard
  - Pierce, Bessie Louise
  - Pierre Lecomte du Nouy Foundation
  - Pierson, Donald
  - Pierson, George Wilson
  - Pierson, Harry H
  - Pierson, R W
  - The Pilgrims of the United States
  - Pilkington, Walter
  - Pimentel, George C
  - Pincoffs, Maurice C
  - Pindar, F V L
  - Piñera, Bernardino
  - Piper, Alan
  - Piper, Henry Dan
  - Pipkin, Charles W
  - Pishmish, Paris
  - Pitcher, Eleanor
  - Pitzer, Mrs. Jean
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S
  - Pizarro, Carlos
  - Platt, E
  - Platt, Eleanor
  - Platt, Mildred Stites
  - Platt, William
  - Plaut, Richard L, Jr.
  - Plaza, Galo
  - Plimpton, Calvin Hastings
  - Plimpton, Francis T P
  - Plymouth Shoe Company
  - Pochmann, Henry A
  - Poe, L Harvey
  - Poffenberger, A T
  - Polaroid Corporation
  - Polk, Theodore W, Jr.
  - Pollack, Peter
  - Pollard, John A
  - Pollock, Thomas Clark
  - Polunin, Nicholas
  - Pomerat, Gerard
  - Pomeroy Company
  - Pomfret, John E
  - Pomfret School
  - Pommellet, Suzanne
  - Ponce, Miguel Boniface
  - Ponter, Herbert
  - Poole, William
  - Pope, Arthur U
  - Pope, Generoso
  - Pope, Isabel
  - Pope, John A
  - Popkin, Anne
  - Portell-Vila, Herminio
  - Porter, David
  - Porter, Mrs. Lois
  - Porter, Quincy
  - Portland Cement Association
  - Portraits, Inc.
  - Porwitzki, Dwight
  - Porwitzki, John
  - Porwitzki, Roy
  - Porwitzki, Theodore
  - Porwitzki, Mrs. Theodore
  - Posner, Ernst
  - Posse, Jorge Escalante
  - Posvar, Wesley W
  - Potter, Carey
  - Potter, Lucy
  - Potter, Russell
  - Pottle, Frederick A
  - Pound, Louise
  - Powell, H L
  - Powell, Thomas Reed
  - Power, Eugene B
  - Powers, Ira C
  - Powers, Philip N
  - Prall, David
  - Prat, Yves
  - Prather, Robert F
  - Pratt, Carroll C
  - Pratt, George D
  - Pratt, John
  - Pratt, Richardson
  - Pratt, Robert A
  - Pratt, W L, III
  - Pratt Institute
  - Pratzner, Laura M
  - Preliminary Memorandum - Brief. Support of the NSDAP by the Industrialists
  - Prendergast, Walter T
  - Prentiss, Richard J, Jr.
  - Presidential consultant
  - Price, Derek de Sola
  - Price, Don K
  - Price, Frederic Newlin
  - Price-Williams, Douglass
  - Priest, Alan
  - Princeton Club
  - Princeton University
  - Pritchard, James B
  - Private foundations - Investments
  - Proctor, Evelyn E S
  - Proffitt, Charles G
  - Progress Products
  - Pruette, Lorine
  - Psacharopoulos, Nikos
  - Puerto Rico - Places to stay
  - Pulley, Charles M
  - Pullman Company
  - Purcell, Mrs. Pearl G
  - Purcell, William H
  - Purdy, Lawson
  - Purdys
  - Purves, Austin, Jr.
  - Purves, Pierre
  - Putnam, Carleton
  - Pyle, Florence M
  - Pyles, Thomas
  - Queens College
  - Quid pro Quo
  - Quillian, Crystal
  - Quimby, Arthur W
  - Quinn, James L
  - Quinn, Lillian A
  - Raban & Son
  - Rabi, I I
  - Radcliffe College
  - Radillo, C M Suarez
  - Radiolevures, Jacquemin
  - Raes, P Alphonsus
  - Railway Express Agency
  - Raines, Alice
  - Rainey, Froelich
  - Ralph Bunche Institute
  - Rambusch, Viggo Bech
  - Ramsdell, Beulah
  - Ramsey, Frederic, Jr.
  - Randall, Philip R
  - Rankin, Rebecca B
  - Ranson, John Crowe
  - Ratchford, Fannie
  - Rath, F L
  - Rath, Mrs. F L, Jr.
  - Rath, R John
  - Rattner, Lawrence
  - Rawls, John
  - Rawson, Kennett L
  - Ray, Dixy Lee
  - Ray, Gordon
  - Ray, John V
  - Read, Helen Appleton
  - Reardon, Gladys
  - Redding, Saunders
  - Redfield, Robert
  - Redman, Mrs. Dagmar
  - Redman, James
  - Redman, Wallace
  - Redmon, Norman
  - Rée, Edward E
  - Reed, Edward B
  - Reed, Joan Phillips
  - Reeves, Ruth
  - Reffes Printing Company
  - Reid, Albert
  - Reid, Frank A
  - Reilly, Frank
  - Reina, Ruben E
  - Reinhardt, Aurelia Henry
  - Reinke, Harrison L
  - Reitoria da Universitade de São Paulo
  - Reitz, J Wayne
  - Remington, Preston
  - Repplier, T S
  - Research Corporation
  - Research Society for Creative Altruism
  - Restrepo de Angél, Maria
  - Rettman, Rosalyn J
  - Rex, Barbara
  - Reyerson, Knowles
  - Reyes, Rodolfo
  - Reynal, Eugene
  - Reynolds, Elizabeth
  - Reynolds, George M
  - Reynolds, J M
  - Reynolds, John F
  - Reynolds, Leighton
  - Reynolds, Roger
  - Reynolds, T M
  - Rhind, Flora M
  - Rhoades, F P
  - Rhoads, Charles J
  - Rhoads, Jonathan E
  - Rhodes, Clarence
  - Rhodes, Mrs. Clarence D
  - Rhodes, Joseph E
  - Rhodes Scholars
    - Grant-in-aid
    - Halifax
    - Political expressions
    - Williams, E T
  - Rhodes Scholarship Trust
  - Rice, Elisabeth
  - Rice, Frank A
  - Rice, John
  - Rich, Daniel Catton
  - Rich, Wilmer Shields
  - Richards, A N
  - Richards, Dickinson W
  - Richards, Francis E
  - Richardson, Charles
  - Richardson, H S
  - Richardson, Ralph W, Jr.
  - Riches, Cromwell A
  - Richmond Greyhound Lines
  - Richter, Curt
  - Richter, Gisela M A
  - Rickens, Gordon
  - Rickey, George
  - Riddle, Dewey
  - Riddle, Oscar
  - Riegger, Wallingford
  - Rieser, Leonard M
  - Rifkind, Simon H
  - Riggs, Lawrason
  - Riley, Stephen T
  - Riley, W Jefferson
  - Rimoldi, H J A
  - Ripley, S Dillon
  - Rippie, Charles W
  - Risso, Don Pablo
  - Ritchie, Andrew Carnduff
  - Ritter, Mary C
  - Ritz Hotel
  - Riveros, Manuel
  - Rizzuto, Antonio
  - Roache, Joel
  - Robbins, J Stanton
  - Robbins, William Jacob
  - Roberts, Alfred W
  - Roberts, Mrs. Helen N
  - Roberts, Isabel
  - Roberts, Laurence P
  - Roberts, Lyle E
  - Roberts, Walter Orr
  - Robins, Thomas
  - Robinson, Geroid Tanquery
  - Rock, Walter J
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette H
  - Rockefeller, David
  - Rockefeller, David, Jr.
  - Rockefeller, John Davidson, III
  - Rockefeller, Laurence S
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund
    - Amateur and professional in the American theatre
    - American theatre today and tomorrow
    - Box office and other earned income
    - Broadway producer
    - Building greater appreciation
    - Chamber music in the U.S.
    - Characteristics and development of the off-Broadway theatre movement
    - Choral music in the U.S.
    - Community arts councils
    - Corporate support for the performing arts
    - Dance in America
    - Directions and management of Arts organizations
    - Economic problems of the American theatre
    - Federal government and the performing arts
    - Federal support for the performing arts
    - Financing the arts
    - Foundation support for the Performing Arts
    - Government and the arts
    - Government support to the performing arts in western Europe
    - Huggin, Nancy
    - The importance of the arts
    - Individual giving
    - Introduction
    - Opera in the United States
    - Performing arts panel
    - Performing arts study
    - Problems confronting the American composer
    - Special studies project
    - Standards and quality
    - State and local government support for the performing arts
    - State of the performing arts - - Today and tomorrow
    - Summary of hearings on economic conditions in the performing arts
    - Symphony orchestras in America
    - Thompson, Helen
    - The University and the professional performing arts
  - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Administration proposed budgets
    - Agenda
    - Agreements and announcements concerning policy and program
    - Agricultural grants program in Latin American
    - Answers to a questionnaire submitted by the select committee of the House of Representatives
    - Appropriations
    - Budget
    - Confidential monthly report
    - Confidential report
    - Declinations
    - Digest of the discussion on the program of the general education board
    - Docket: Executive Committee meeting
    - Docket: Meetings
    - Docket: Trustees meetings
    - Econometrics
    - Expense account: H.A.Moe
    - Financial policy
    - Financial report
    - Foundation's experience with refugee scholars
    - The future of the general education board
    - Hookworms campaigns in North Carolina
    - History of Foundation program
    - Humanities program
    - International health
    - Japanese literary fellowship program
    - Louisville project
    - Malaria and malaria eradication
    - Medical care
    - Memorandum...to Dean Rusk
    - Minutes
    - Minutes of annual meeting
    - Minutes of executive committee
    - Minutes of Trustees
    - Monthly report
    - Notes on Indian agriculture
    - Notes on program
    - Plans for future work
    - Program in linguistics and language study
    - Report
    - Report of commission on review of the international health division
    - Report of commission...to China to study...development of medicine and public health
    - Report of special committee on policy and program
    - Report of the exploratory committee on financing higher education and research
    - Report on Germany
    - Report to the trustees
    - Retirement
    - Sayles
    - Schedule of authorizations
    - Scholarships and the Mexican Revolution in agricultural science
    - Selected resolutions and agreements of the trustees supplementing the constitution and by-laws
    - Some observations on Soviet Industrial growth
    - Supplementary
    - Supplementary statement relating to the request from the general education board
    - Trustees meeting
    - Villa Serbelloni
  - Rockefeller Institute
  - Rockefeller University
  - Rocker, R
  - Rockey, Keller
  - Rodgers, Mrs. Dorothy
  - Roe, Anne
  - Roeder, Kenneth D
  - Rogers, Bruce
  - Rogers, Burton Brush
  - Rogers, J Theodore
  - Rogers, Mrs. J Theodore
  - Rogers, James Gamble
  - Rogers, Lindsay
  - Rogers, Stuart
  - Rogers, Walter S
  - Romer, Alfred S
  - Ronan, Erna Vinadé
  - Ronan, William J
  - Ronan, Mrs. William J
  - Rood, Mrs. John
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas
  - Roosevelt, P James
  - Root, Elihu
  - Roothbert, Albert
  - Roothbert Fund
  - Roper, Elmo
  - Rord, John
  - Rorimer, James J
  - Rorimer, James L
  - Rosenbaum, Mrs. Edna
  - Rosenbaum, Samuel R
  - Rosenblueth, Arturo
  - Rosenblueth, Virginia T
  - Rosenthal, A
  - Rosenwald, Lessing J
  - Roskill, S W
  - Ross, Emory
  - Rossell, Eva D
  - Rostagno, Victor
  - Rotch, Mrs. Arthur
  - Rothbard, C
  - Roudebush, Francis W
  - Rouleau, Ernest
  - Roundabout Theatre
  - Roura-Parella, Juan
  - Rous, Peyton
  - Rowan, Edward B
  - Rowe, James W
  - Rowe, L S
  - Rowell, Henry T
  - Rowell, Hugh Grant
  - Royal Seed Establishment
  - Royal Society of Arts and Manufactures
  - Royal Society of London
  - Rubinow
  - Rudolf, Paul M
  - Ruebhausen, Oscar M
  - Ruff, Carl
  - Rugg, Harold G
  - Ruggles, Mrs. Anne
  - Ruhemann, Helmut
  - Ruml, Beardsley
  - Rundle, Walter C
  - Ruopp, Richard R
  - Rush, Charles E
  - Rusinow, Dennison I
  - Rusk, Dean
  - Rusk, Howard A
  - Russell, F F
  - Russell, Franklin Ferriss
  - Russell, John F
  - Russell, John M
  - Russell, William H
  - Russell Sage Foundation
  - Russo, Alexander
  - Rutherford, Pearl
  - Ruud, Johan T
  - Ryan, George J
  - Ryan, J Joseph
  - Ryan, John J
  - Ryan, Lawrence V
  - Ryerson, Knowles A
  - Rypins, Stanley
  - Ryscamp, Charles
  - Sachs, Paul J
  - Saint Augustine, Florida, 400th anniversary
  - Saint Louis Post Dispatch
  - Sakimura, K
  - Salas, Eugenio Pereira
  - Salas-Viu, Vincente
  - Salemme, Antonio
  - Salisbury, William
  - Salk Institute
  - Saltzman, Charles E
  - Salvatore, Victor
  - Sammons, Wheeler
  - Samper, Leonor
  - Sandberg, William
  - Sanders, John C
  - Sandford, Sir F H
  - Sands, Bonnie
  - Sanford, R A
  - Santa Cruz, Domingo
  - Sarlat, Abraham
  - Sarlat Printing Service
  - Sarnoff, David